Inventory of the Addition to the Papers of Daniel J. Meador, 1963-1985
University of Virginia, Arthur J. Morris Law Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Law Library
Addition to the Papers of Daniel J. Meador, 1963-1985
Special Collections, University of Virginia Law Library
MSS 82-3a
This collection consists of 6 boxes.
This addition to the Meador papers consists of correspondence, committee files, and other professional working papers.
Administrative Information
Access
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Professor Meador gave this addition of the papers to the library in 1986.
Contents List
- General Correspondence 1976-1982, 8 folders (Box 1)
- General Correspondence 1982-1985, 5 folders (Box 2)
- General Information 1977-1983, 5 folders (Box 2)
- Center for Law and National Security Committee 1981-1984 (Box 3)
- Confidential Honor System Poll n.d. (Box 3)
- Curriculum Committee 1979-1982, 2 folders (Box 3)
- Dillard papers 1984 (Box 3)
- Ewald Chair Committee 1981-1983 (Box 3)
- Farmer Memorial Fund 1981-1983 (Box 3)
- Graduate Committee 1981-1983 (Box 3)
- Journal of law and politics Committee 1982-1985 (Box 3)
- Law Review 1979 (Box 3)
- Moot Court 1982-1983 (Box 3)
- "National Character" of Admissions Committee 1978 (Box 3)
- Part-time Student Committee 1980-1982 (Box 3)
- Procedures Committee 1985 (Box 3)
- Summer School for Lawyers Committee Personal Files 1983-1984 (Box 3)
- General Correspondence 1965, 1969-1977, 2 folders (Box 4)
- Alabama Court of Criminal Appeals 1973, 1975 (Box 4)
- American Academy of Judicial Education 1971-1977 (Box 4)
- American Academy of Judicial Education Judicial Writing Program 1973-1976, 2 folders (Box 4)
- American Judicature Society 1972-1977 (Box 4)
- American Society for Legal History 1967-1977, 2 folders (Box 5)
- Appellate Court Administrative Seminar 1976 (Box 5)
- Attorney General-Miscellaneous 1977-1979 (Box 5)
- Datebooks 1977-1979 (Box 5)
- Federal Judicial Center 1971-1974 (Box 5)
- Fulbright and Guggenheim Foundations 1963-1977 (Box 6)
- Justice on Appeal 1975-1977, 2 folders (Box 6)
- National Conference on Appellate Justice 1973-1975 (Box 6)
- Prelude to Gideon 1980-1982, Venue Legislation 1966-1971 (Box 6)